* Search

Ezoic Services
==============

This website has an exclusive advertising contract with Ezoic Inc. (“Ezoic”), a renowned leader in website optimization, enhancing user experiences, optimizing ad performance, and generating revenue through advanced AI-powered technology.  
Ezoic Services  
This website uses the services of Ezoic Inc. (“Ezoic”), including to manage third-party interest-based advertising. Ezoic may employ a variety of technologies on this website, including tools to serve content, display advertisements and enable advertising to visitors of this website, which may utilize first and third-party cookies.  
A cookie is a small text file sent to your device by a web server that enables the website to remember information about your browsing activity. First-party cookies are created by the site you are visiting, while third-party cookies are set by domains other than the one you're visiting. Ezoic and our partners may place third-party cookies, tags, beacons, pixels, and similar technologies to monitor interactions with advertisements and optimize ad targeting. Please note that disabling cookies may limit access to certain content and features on the website, and rejecting cookies does not eliminate advertisements but will result in non-personalized advertising. You can find more information about cookies and how to manage them [here](https://allaboutcookies.org/). The following information may be collected, used, and stored in a cookie when serving personalized ads:  

* IP address
* Operating system type and version
* Device type
* Language preferences
* Web browser type
* Email (in a hashed or encrypted form)

Ezoic and its partners may use this data in combination with information that has been independently collected to deliver targeted advertisements across various platforms and websites. Ezoic’s partners may also gather additional data, such as unique IDs, advertising IDs, geolocation data, usage data, device information, traffic data, referral sources, and interactions between users and websites or advertisements, to create audience segments for targeted advertising across different devices, browsers, and apps. You can find more information about interest-based advertising and how to manage them [here](https://youradchoices.com/).  
You can view Ezoic’s privacy policy [here](https://ezoic.com/privacy/), or for additional information about Ezoic’s advertising and other partners, you can view Ezoic’s advertising partners [here.](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/)

============================================================================

[We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed](https://www.ezoic.com/privacy-policy/advertising-partners/) [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/linuxandubuntu.com).

Who we are
----------

Our website address is: https://www.linuxandubuntu.com.

We share applications, themes, icons and scripts, most of the stuff belong outside of linuxandubuntu.com and copyright owned by their respective owners. So we test applications and other stuff before releasing to the public. If you install something from linuxandubuntu.com, in that case, linuxandubuntu isn’t responsible for any loss/damage/discomfort occurred as a result of using stuff from linuxandubuntu (BTW we test everything at least once on our computers, we never release anything to the public if there are problems in Applications/stuff).  
  
Any trademarks or logos used in this site are the property of their respective owners.  
  
Any personal info provided to us, will not be shared with anyone outside linuxandubuntu.com. We don’t spam and never sell personal data to any individual/company/third-party.  
  
linuxandubuntu.com isn’t responsible for externally linked sites. We recommend you to read the privacy policy of linked sites before disclosing any personal information to them.  
  
**Your browser can turn-off our cookies or selectively third-party cookies or disable cookies within settings**

However, this step will affect your browser interaction with our website as well as other websites.

What personal data we collect and why we collect it
---------------------------------------------------

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you visit our login page, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

* * *

LinuxAndUbuntu Newsletter
-------------------------

Join the newsletter to receive the latest updates in your inbox.

Your email address  Subscribe

Please check your inbox and click the link to confirm your subscription.

Please enter a valid email address!

An error occurred, please try again later.

Featured Posts
--------------

[### ChatGPT Alternatives: Exploring Free, Open-Source and Affordable AI Models

18 Jul 2024](https://www.linuxandubuntu.com/home/chatgpt-alternatives-free-open-source-ai-models/)

----------------------------------------------------

LinuxAndUbuntu

LinuxAndUbuntu is a blog dedicated to help new users learn Linux. We regularly post Linux tips, tricks, and hacks to educate you about the best operating system, Linux.

Navigation

Newsletter

Your email address  Subscribe

Please check your inbox and click the link to confirm your subscription.

Please enter a valid email address!

An error occurred, please try again later.

© 2024 LinuxAndUbuntu - Published with [Ghost](https://ghost.org/) & Powered by [MassiveGRID](https://portal.massivegrid.com/link.php?id=2)

[](https://statcounter.com/ "Web Analytics
Made Easy - Statcounter")
